Francesca Dick

07734387436 <u>fhd96@hotmail.co.uk</u> Bristol, BS4 2QP https://www.linkedin.com/in/frankie-d-aab176180

Profile

I'm an experienced IT technician and Tech Recruiter with years of professional practice in problem solving.

I bring an enthusiastic and positive upbeat energy to the workplace whilst still making sure we soar in terms of results and productivity.

After 8 years as a hardware and software technician I moved into recruitment where I specialised in developers & engineers along with many other tech diciplines. I supported a range of roles including those of a senior/executive level.

I'm currently doing an undergraduate degree in Computer Science (Software Development) as I find myself drawn to this area of study and enjoy learning.

I was one of the first in the UK to be given the title of tech expert at Apple as it was a brand new role which requires me to not only handle Genius Bar appointments, diagnose, take apart and fix Apple products but is also a mentorship and leadership heavy role.

Experience

SPECIALIST TECHNOLOGY RECRUITMENT CONSULTANT, ADLIB, BRISTOL - JULY 2022 - PRESENT

I work across a range of specialist disciplines including Development/Engineering, QA / Testing, DevOps, Infrastructure, CTOs / Tech Leaders and much more. I bring a regional focus covering the South West, South Coast, Midlands and Wales, but can support with fully remote roles too. I specialise in supporting Software Houses, Tech Consultancies, Household Brands, start-ups and scale-ups, B Corps, Tech4Goods and GreenTech / Sustainability specialists.

TECHNICAL EXPERT, APPLE (VARIOUS LOCATIONS) - JUNE 2017 - JULY 2022

I am expected to guide the other technicians with their knowledge and lead them to hit targets set out by the company. I'm often leader on the floor for the Genius Bar so I have experience in floor management in a stressful and busy retail environment. My role requires that I make sound decisions both on the floor and operationally. This role also includes a lot of operational planning as we deal with a large number of serialised repair parts and products aswell as some scheduling.

Responsibilities include mentoring and training the team, resolving customer issues, repairing iPhones, doing appointments at the Genius Bar for all Apple devices and being one of the iOS experts in the store. Since starting this role I have achieved consistently good results both personally and as part of the team.

ASSISTANT PRODUCER, APPLE MUSIC 1 (TILEYARD) - JUNE 2019 - NOVEMBER 2019

During my time here I have learnt the ins and outs of radio production as well as content capture (for Apple Music) for artists. I would often be a part of high profile meetings with music artists and label representatives. My responsibilities have included; planning shows, cleaning tracks, editing and building promo's and liners for

shows, assisting with recording Artist lead shows (such as Jax Jones' House Work Radio), building music news, dealing with metadata and various other jobs.

TECHNICAL SPECIALIST, APPLE (VARIOUS LOCATIONS) - 2014 - JUNE 2017

Responsibilities included doing appointments at the genius bar and repairing relationships between the customers and the company.

BAKERY ASSISTANT, SAINSBURYS - 2013 - 2014

Responsibilities included serving customers at the counter, packaging and slicing bread, processing reductions at the end of the day and stocking shelves.

HICKIES MUSIC STORE - AUGUST 2012 - FEBRUARY 2013

Responsibilities included cleaning and tidying the store, doing demo's of instruments to customers and processing sales.

Education

Open University (2021 - Present) - Cyber Security BSC (currently taking this course)

Kingston University (2015 - 2018) – BSc Pharmacology

The Sixth Form college Farnborough - Maths, Further Maths, Chemistry, Human Biology

Bearwood College - 10 GCSE's graded A* - B

Skills

Computer and electronic device repair, problem solving, composure, dealing with ambiguity, conflict management, learning on the fly.

Other

I have been producing art such as music and dance since I was a child and I was a part of a small team that organised and ran large scale events (in a college with 3000+ students) throughout my time at College. I've played instruments since the age of 6 and I am currently learning a second language. I have been teaching a dance class in central London and Bristol for the last 3 years which has shown me how to adapt my teaching and mentoring style when necessary.

References

Available upon request.